can you grow a small trading account the
answer is yes I actually did it I turned
$100 to about
$360,000 now I don't recommend to do
that at all that was gambling that was
not real trading and that's not what I'm
going to teach you in this video in this
video I'm going to teach you how to grow
an account properly so you can make
money with a very little account and you
can grow it month over month I'm going
to teach you all the things that you
need to know so you can grow a small
account properly so let me just give you
guys some context let's say you have
$100 $500 and you want to grow it in
trading right there's only two ways for
you to do it the first way is you got to
gamble it you're going to pretty much
bet 100% of the account and hopefully
try and take it to $11,000 $10,000 or
whatever you want to take it to which is
not recommendable and the odds of you
failing are very high and then the other
is going to be a very very slow marathon
on a percentage based growth week after
week month after month which is the real
way of trading and in this video I'm
going to teach you the tips on how to do
that correctly and this is something
that 90% of the traders in the industry
do not do correctly simply because they
don't know the basis of growing an
account properly that's because a lot of
Traders they think becoming a successful
Trader of profitable Trader is when they
turn 100 bucks to 10,000 or turning 300
to 30,000 whatever actually crazy story
is Jordan one of my top students now
which is crazy he for his first two
years of trading he thought that he
would only become a profitable Trader
once he turned $500 to $10,000 he was 2
years trying to do this and he took the
$5 00 to about 800 then to about 2,000
then he would blow it and he would do it
back and forth for about 2 years and he
never made any money and he and I I met
him one day and then he was like bro I I
keep winning trades but I'm not a
profitable Trader because I haven't
turned the 500 to 10,000 I'm like dude
because you turn $500 to$ 10,000 that
does not make you a profitable Trader
that makes you if anything you got a
very good winning streak and you got
very lucky and you know you probably
took the right trades and avoided the
wrong ones but that doesn't mean you're
a profitable Trader you're profitable
Trader when out of 10 trades you win
four and then you lose six those four
trades you win double of what you lose
so very simple example 10 trades you
lose six you risk 1% that's minus 6% but
these four trades that you win let's say
you win 2% 2 4 6 8 so now you have just
made back the 6% that you have lost and
now you are 2% profitable that is a
profitable Trader not somebody that's
earned 500 bucks 10 ,000 that's not how
you grow an account you grow an account
on the percentage basis on the account
and that actually leads me to my next
point which to grow an account it is
extremely crucial on the number amount
of Trades that you take you will be
surprised how many of you guys I meet in
person and you guys ask me how many
trades should I take when trading a
funded account or personal account or
whatever should I take a lot of trades
or should I take a little bit on good
quality of Trades and I almost revers
the question back to you guys what do
you think makes more sense let's say
you're playing basketball and you have a
bunch of defenders in front of you and
you just shoot the shot every single
time from a three-point shot and just
try and make as many as you can every
single time you get the ball or does it
make more sense to wait when you are
open by the free throw line or even get
a shot at the free throw line and then
you take your time there and then you
shoot it what do you think makes more
sense obviously the free throw obviously
the open shot now does that happen more
often than every single time you get the
ball no that's why the odds of you
making a shot from the free throw line
or when you're open is a lot higher than
when you have a defender in front of you
what does that require patience requires
patience for you to wait until you're
open so you get the ball and you can
shoot it it's the same exact thing in
trading those good quality types of
Trades they come but you have to be
patient you have to wait for the market
to give you that good quality trade so
then you can take it just because you
have the ability to take a trade every
single time doesn't mean that you should
just because every single time you get
the ball you're able to shoot it doesn't
mean that you should you have to wait
for the best quality moments to then
execute on the position and you almost
have to like shift your mindset to start
looking for trading opportunities not
taking a trade a trading opportunity is
an opportunity to make money taking a
trade is just getting involved in the
market just to get involved I treat
every single trading opportunity as an
opportunity to grow my account it's a
business decision it's a logical
decision that's going to make me money
I'm not doing it to get involved or to
entertain myself with something
everything that I do is with a purpose I
had a very strict decision behind it not
just taking a random decision because I
just want to feel like I'm involved that
is actually literally how I had my
biggest trading day about 2 months ago I
made
$363,000 in one single trade you think
that comes every single day no I waited
about 2 weeks for that trade to set
itself up and I waited about a whole
entire week for the trade to complete
itself so I took my time because I
treated it as an opportunity
in the market There's an opportunity to
capitalize off of this market movement
not just a trade to click a buy or sell
button to feel like I'm doing something
and how you can do this is by having the
same mindset that I obtained that is by
treating pretty much the rest of your
trading career your trading life as if
you were to have one punch card and in
that punch card you only get about 20
trades there are only 20 trades that you
can take for the rest of your life I can
guarantee you you're going to be very
selective on the amount of Trades that
you're going to take you're not going to
take any random trades what is that
going to lead you to do it's going to
lead you to take the best type of Trades
that you possibly can in return you're
going to make a lot more money cuz
you're only focusing on what matters but
now what if I double that for you let's
say I give you two Punch Cards one is
going to be a demo punch card which
you're going to pretty much have a free
20 test trades for the trades that
you're going to take for the rest of
your life and those 20 trades that you
test on that first demo punch card the
winning trades that you capitalize off
of there and you learn from them you're
going to take those then to the real
punch card that you're going to use for
the rest of your life so now in those
first 20 trades you have just realized
the ones that work and the ones that
don't so the mistakes that you made
there you don't make them ever again now
you only focus on this real punch card
on the winning ones that you tested out
on that demo punch card that I gave you
at the beginning what is that going to
create for you on this real life punch
card the odds of your success rate are
going to grow so much that I wish I
learned this so early on in my journey
it would have saved me so much time and
so many losses and this is not me just
saying this or making something up I
actually got this from one of the best
investors in the face of the planet
Warren Buffett I've told students if
when they got out of school they got a
punch card with 20 punches on it and
that's all the investment decisions they
got to make in their entire life they
would get very rich because they would
think very hard about each one he set
the example with only one punch card but
then I almost was like well if you only
get one punch card for 20 trades for the
rest of your life how do you know what
mistakes to avoid and which ones to
learn from well what if you actually get
two Punch Cards 20 to test out to see
what works and what doesn't and then
once you learn from that then you go
into the real market and treat it as if
you only had 20 trades for the rest of
your life now that takes me to the next
Point once you understand that you only
have 20 trades to pretty much take for
the rest of your life you have to risk a
calculated percentage on these trades
now it's not going to be 1% or 2% when
you want to grow a $500 account to let's
say $1,000 that's honestly not realistic
and it'll take you years for that to
happen the percentage that you should be
risking if you're taking very quality
amount of Trades and very little amounts
during the weeks or even months should
be risking anywhere in between 5 and 10%
because let's be honest for you to take
$500 to about $10,00 000 you're going to
have to up your risk a little bit in
order for it to even make sense for you
and the risk tolerance at about 10% from
a $500 account it's only $50 so it's
very doable risk I think for anybody
that is going to get involved in the
space of investing because let's be
honest you need money to make money it's
the realistic of this business and keep
in mind the money that you put into this
trading account you almost have to think
that it's gone as if you already lost
the money or if you already blew it
because you cannot be attached to the
window wi or losses every single time I
win a trade I say cool that's the reason
why I took the trade and every single
time I lose a trade I say cool that's
why I only risk a certain percentage of
the account you have to be extremely
nonchalant on whatever outcome the trade
is going to have for you that's why the
money that you put into your trading
account how I like to say you set and
forget it just forget about it as a
whole put it in there treat it as an
investment and every single trade it's
an investment opportunity and guys
please do not invest your rent money
unless it's somebody money who gives a
put it in there doesn't matter s
and forget it and the point is hit the
Subscribe button the Subscribe button is
here here hit the Subscribe button
either side cuz we have more videos like
this coming every single week so hit the
Subscribe button so now let's actually
set a real scenario of what $500 can
take you with a very simple win rate and
a very simple percentage approach to
this account again this is something
very realistic and very doable so let's
say you have a starting balance of $500
on your account you're going to risk
let's say 10% per trade on this account
so let's say you have a 50% win rate
meaning out of 10 trades you win five
then you lose five that means that you
would have lost
$50 on the first five trades if you
would have lost them all in one and then
the next five trades you would have won
so you would have made a total of 20% on
each and every single one of these
trades so you would have made a total of
$500 on these five trades that you win
so you just made back the $ 250 that you
just lost here and then you just made an
extra $ 250 on top of the money you just
made back now leaving your account at
$750 so you just scaled from $500 to 750
with taking 10 simple trades and this
could happen within a month so now this
is where a lot of Traders would want to
then withdraw that money or start
risking more and the answer is no you
need to stick to the same exact
percentage so if you started off the
account with 10% risk you stick with
that to the account you decide to
withdraw and start a new one you cannot
lower the risk doesn't matter how many
losses you take and you cannot upper
risk how many wins you take this is
crucial to having the consistent growth
on the account and you have
sustainability and you can successfully
grow your account over time so that
might not seem like much because it's a
$500 account but now this is where the
game changes they say you add a zero to
the end of that well you just took a
$5,000 account to
$7,500 within one month us just made
$2500 by literally winning half of the
time literally 10 trades you lose five
you win 5 and you just made $2,500 which
is very simple and very doable in the
market and now it gets even crazier when
you add another zero you would have
literally taken a $50,000 account to a
$75,000 account and notice how nothing
changes it's the same percentage same
trades same win rate same loss rate same
everything the only thing that changes
is the dollar amount behind the
percentage the key to this game to
become successful is the percentage game
so you're literally just playing with
percentages and the hundreds tens of
thousands of dollars are going to follow
but now I actually want to take it back
a step let's go back to the $5,000
example not the $500 example because
realistically it's not much and the
$50,000 is too much it's that's going to
make sense in just a second the $5,000
is about the right point for you to
pretty much leave a job and make extra
income from Trading where you can pretty
much live from it forever so a lot of
you guys might be like oh but $5,000 is
too much and I don't have access to that
well what if I told you that you can
actually get access to $5,000
with5 of the $500 that you would start
on your small account you can literally
purchase a challenge for $5,000 which
will cost you about 100 bucks 120 bucks
so then if you were to pass a challenge
you will literally get funded $5,000
like they will literally give you the
money if you are proven to be a
successful Trader all you have to do is
have about $100 $120 to purchase this
challenge so getting access to the
$5,000 is not difficult at all if you
are a successful uccessful Trader you
can purchase any account size with any
of these prop firms and you can
literally get hundreds of thousands of
dollars just thrown at you because you
have this profitable skill set the hard
thing here is the profitable skill set
it's the hard thing to obtain for a
person to master and Conquer because
nobody wants to be patient and apply
these simple rules on how to grow an
account this literally can apply to a
personal account it can apply to a
personal accounts it is literally the
same percentage game the only thing that
changes on the dollar amount is a dollar
amount behind the percentage of the
account and what if I told you getting
access to this skill set is probably as
easy or even easier than getting access
to these $5,000 the skill set has become
even easier to understand and for any
beginner Trader to actually Master it
and Conquer it and make trading either
an added part of their income or even
their full-time income from trading this
is where the set and forget strategy
comes in and UNS Traders make anywhere
from $1,000 to
$11,500 a week using the set and forget
strategy that has made me $10 million in
the last four years of trading now
you're probably wondering what set and
forget is or you've never heard about it
all you have to do is click the link
below and I have a video there for you
that explains to you exactly what set
and forget is and how it lets thousands
of members be able to make anywhere from
a th000 to $1,500 a week using the set
forget strategy and this is very very
simple concept that is going to teach
you how to grow your accounts from 500
to 1,000 to 1,000 to 10,000 it's the
same strategy that let me turn $100 to
$300,000 so if you guys want to know
more about it make sure you guys click
the link in the description below you
guys watch the whole entire s forget
video so you see if it suits for you
appreciate you guys watching this video
all the way to the end make sure you
guys hit that like And subscribe button
and I'll see you guys in the next video